

About Me

Date of birth: 25/09/1993

Algeciras, Cádiz

I am a graduate in Translation and Interpreting (EN/DE-ES) specialized in Audiovisual Translation and currently studying a Full Stack Development bootcamp. My aim is to find challenging experiences that provide me with daily learning and a dynamic and friendly environment with a great team spirit.

Job Experience

10/2020 - 05/2022 Administrative Assistant at Almacenamiento del Frío y Logística

del Sur (Algeciras - Cádiz)

04/2019 - 05/2020: Waitress at Pizzeria Is Morus (Alphen aan den Rijn, NL)

01/2019 - 05/2019: Camarera en Horeca Nu en Vijf Mei Sporthal (Leiden, NL)

08/2017 - 05/2018: Sales and Marketing Assistant at JD Sports (Amsterdam, NL)

03/2017 - 07/2018: Bartender at The Waterhole Rock Music Bar (Amsterdam, NL)

01/2016 - 05/2016: Translator and editor at EARRES (Granada)

12/2015 - 03/2016: Retail seller at GAME Digital Plc (La Zubia, Granada)

Education

Full Stack Development Bootcamp

May-July 2022 Upgrade Hub

2016 - 2018 Master degree in Audiovisual Translation (English — Spanish)

Universidad de Cádiz

2011 - 2015 Degree in Translation and Interpreting (English/German— Spanish)

Universidad de Córdoba

Language Skills	Understanding		Speaking	Writing
	Listening	Reading		
English	C1	C2 CERTIFICADO DE	C1 INGLÉS AVANZADO (CA	C1 .E) B1
French	Cambridge College Junio 2010			
Dutch	Al	A2	A2	Al
German	B1	В1	ВІ	A2
	Al	A2	A2	A1
			•	

Contact info:

glorvega93@gmail.com

670 84 82 77

in @gloria-vega-berna

https://github.com/glorvega